import 'package:isro_quiz/Quiz/QuestionModel.dart';

final questions = [
  Question(id: 1,
      question: 'Which planet is known as the ‘Watery Planet’ ?',
      correct_answer: 'Earth',
      incorrect_answers: ['Mercury','Mars','Jupiter']),
  Question(id: 2,
      question: 'Messenger satellite has been launched by NASA for the study of',
      correct_answer: 'Mercury',
      incorrect_answers: ['Venus','Saturn','Jupiter']),
  Question(id: 3,
      question: 'Which of the following is indicated by the colour of a star?',
      correct_answer: 'Temperature',
      incorrect_answers: ['Weight','Distance','Size']),
  Question(id: 4,
      question: 'Milky Way Galaxy was first seen by',
      correct_answer: 'Galileo',
      incorrect_answers: ['Martin Schmidt','Marconi','Newton']),
  Question(id: 5,
      question: 'Halley’s comet appears once in a period of ________',
      correct_answer: '76 years',
      incorrect_answers: ['24 years','32 years','84 years']),
  Question(id: 6,
      question: 'The radiant energy of the sun is transmitted in the form of ________',
      correct_answer: 'Short waves',
      incorrect_answers: ['Long waves','Particles','None of these']),
  Question(id: 7,
      question: '“Sirius”, the brightest star outside of the Solar System, is also called ________.',
      correct_answer: 'Dog star',
      incorrect_answers: ['Cat star','Fox star','Lion star']),
  Question(id: 8,
      question: 'The largest of the planets is',
      correct_answer: 'Jupiter',
      incorrect_answers: ['Saturn','Uranus','Neptune']),
  Question(id: 9,
      question: 'Who of the following discovered the laws of planetary orbits?',
      correct_answer: 'Johannes Kepler',
      incorrect_answers: ['Galileo Galilei','Nicholas Copernicus','Isaac Newton']),
  Question(id: 10,
      question: 'Which of the following is called “Blue Planet”?',
      correct_answer: 'Earth',
      incorrect_answers: ['Saturn','Jupiter','Mars']),
];